Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم الإدارة، شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
(In my entire life.)
(طوال حياتي.)
(The lover was heartless.)
(كان العاشق قاسي القلب.)
(May the Shen family's injustice be cleared.)
(نسأل الله أن ينصف عائلة شين من الظلم الذي لحق بها.)
(My friends was traitorous.)
(كان صديقي خائناً.)
(The family gate was slaughtered.)
(تم ذبح أفراد العائلة الذين كانوا يعيشون في المنزل.)
(I hate that I trusted the wrong person.)
(أكره أنني وثقت بالشخص الخطأ.)
(Hate that I was powerless to protect my parents.)
(أكره أنني كنت عاجزاً عن حماية والديّ.)
(But I'm not willing.)
(لكنني لست مستعداً).
(I'm not willing to be forever trapped at the bottom of an icy lake.)
(لست مستعداً لأن أبقى محاصراً إلى الأبد في قاع بحيرة جليدية.)
(Not willing that the Shen family continues to bear this stain.)
(غير راغبين في أن تستمر عائلة شين في تحمل هذه الوصمة.)
(More unwilling)
(أكثر عزوفاً)
(that the killers who harmed others roam free.)
(أن القتلة الذين ألحقوا الأذى بالآخرين يتجولون أحراراً.)
(If there truly is a deity in this world,)
(إن كان هناك إله حقاً في هذا العالم،)
(I am willing to offer my soul,)
(أنا على استعداد لتقديم روحي،)
(even if I fall to hell for all eternity.)
(حتى لو سقطت في الجحيم إلى الأبد.)
(The Shen clan)
(عشيرة شين)
(also must be granted a chance to avenge and clear its name.)
(كما يجب منحها فرصة للثأر وتبرئة اسمها).
=The Architect=
=المهندس المعماري=
=Episode 1= (I'll forge my hate into a blade)
=الحلقة 1= (سأحول كراهيتي إلى نصل)
Matron Li.
شركة ماترون المحدودة
How could she have been resurrected?
كيف أمكن إعادتها إلى الحياة؟
Your Highness.
صاحب السمو.
(Governor's Residence's Dancer, Xi Yan) This lowly dancer,
(راقصة قصر الحاكم، شي يان) هذه الراقصة المتواضعة،
Xi Yan is alive again?
(راقصة مقر إقامة الحاكم، شي يان) هل عادت شي يان إلى الحياة؟
What's going on?
ماذا يحدث هنا؟
(Daliang Princess, Li Wan'er)
(أميرة داليانغ، لي وان إير)
Li Wan'er.
لي وان إير.
I thought I was already dead.
ظننت أنني قد مت بالفعل.
How dare a lowly dancer like you,
كيف تجرؤ راقصة وضيعة مثلك؟
Xi Yan address me
شي يان، خاطبني
by noble title?
باللقب النبيل؟
(Lowly dancer?)
(راقصة متواضعة؟)
(Xi Yan?)
(شي يان؟)
(I clearly am Shen Changning, eldest daughter of the Shen family.)
(من الواضح أنني شين تشانغنينغ، الابنة الكبرى لعائلة شين.)
(How could I appear here like this?)
(كيف لي أن أظهر هنا هكذا؟)
Lowly maid, Xi Yan.
الخادمة المتواضعة، شي يان.
(Shen family's legitimate daughter, Shen Changning)
(الابنة الشرعية لعائلة شين، شين تشانغنينغ)
(Prince Duan's eldest son, Xiao Huaijin)
(الابن الأكبر للأمير دوان، شياو هوايجين)
(How did I turn into Xi Yan's appearance?)
(كيف تحولت إلى مظهر شي يان؟)
How dare you climb into the Governor's bed?
كيف تجرؤ على التسلل إلى فراش الحاكم؟
Today I will drown you alive,
سأغرقك اليوم وأنت حي،
only then will my heart's hatred be solved.
عندها فقط ستُحل كراهية قلبي .
Your struggle is useless.
إن كفاحك لا طائل منه.
(Li Wan'er.)
(لي وان إير.)
(After all we called ourselves sisters once.)
(بعد كل شيء، كنا نسمي أنفسنا أخوات في يوم من الأيام.)
(When the Shen family fell, you stabbed me in the back.)
(عندما سقطت عائلة شين، طعنتني في ظهري.)
(You betrayed me from behind.)
(لقد خنتني من الخلف.)
(Now that we have this second chance.)
(الآن وقد أتيحت لنا هذه الفرصة الثانية.)
(I will not let go peacefully.)
(لن أترك الأمر يسير بسلام.)
How dare you!
كيف تجرؤ!
Help!
يساعد!
How could I be so blind-sighted to not see one's true nature?
كيف لي أن أكون غافلاً إلى هذا الحد عن رؤية الطبيعة الحقيقية لشخص ما؟
How could I be deaf to warnings?
كيف لي أن أتجاهل التحذيرات؟
How could I be blind in my heart to distinguish good from evil?
كيف لي أن أكون أعمى في قلبي عن التمييز بين الخير والشر؟
Under Li Wan'er's human skin,
تحت جلد لي وان إير البشري،
what are you really?
ما أنت حقاً؟
(Pei Yu.)
(باي يو.)
(Your hands are stained with Shen family's blood.)
(يداك ملطختان بدماء عائلة شين.)
(The vendetta of our clans' purge)
(ثأر تطهير عشائرنا)
(and the hatred of the clan's eradication are irreconcilable.)
(وكراهية إبادة العشيرة أمر لا يمكن التوفيق بينه).
(Daliang Governor, Pei Yu) (I'll skin you and break your bones)
(حاكم داليانغ، باي يو) (سأسلخ جلدك وأكسر عظامك)
(to repay blood with blood)
(رد الدم بالدم)
(Shen Changning's Father) (and reborn anew.)
(والد شين تشانغنينغ) (وولد من جديد).
(Shen Changning's Mother)
(والدة شين تشانغنينغ)
(The lives I take from you)
(الأرواح التي أزهقها منك)
(will be my reason to live.)
(سيكون هذا سبب وجودي في الحياة.)
Lowly maid!
خادمة حقيرة!
- Your Lordship.
- يا صاحب السعادة.
Yu, this lowly maid was bullying me.
يو، هذه الخادمة الحقيرة كانت تتنمر عليّ.
Disrespectful uprising
انتفاضة غير محترمة
deserves death.
يستحق الموت.
Drag her away.
اسحبها بعيداً.
Governor Pei.
الحاكم باي.
They say the Governor can't tell loyalty from betrayal,
يقولون إن الحاكم لا يستطيع التمييز بين الولاء والخيانة.
and cannot tell good from evil.
ولا يستطيع التمييز بين الخير والشر.
Seems like that's true.
يبدو أن هذا صحيح.
I just
أنا فقط
saw something dirty in the princess's hair
رأى شيئًا قذرًا في شعر الأميرة
and tried to brush it off for her,
وحاول أن يتجاهل الأمر من أجلها.
but the princess reacted fiercely.
لكن الأميرة ردت بشدة.
That's how the misunderstanding happened.
هكذا حدث سوء الفهم.
Lowly maid, you still dare to argue?
يا خادمة الحقيرة، أما زلتِ تجرؤين على الجدال؟
Yu.
يو.
Such a lowly maid with malicious intent.
خادمة حقيرة ذات نوايا خبيثة.
If not executed...
إذا لم يتم تنفيذه...
Your Highness.
صاحب السمو.
Did you not feel something crawling in your hair?
ألم تشعر بشيء يزحف في شعرك؟
If you don't brush it away now, it will crawl into your clothes.
إذا لم تتخلص منه الآن، فسوف يتسلل إلى ملابسك.
Grub?
نكش؟
Your Highness.
صاحب السمو.
Didn't expect you still have a side like this.
لم أتوقع أن يكون لديك جانب كهذا.
You have indeed made me underestimate you.
لقد جعلتني بالفعل أستهين بك.
I'm just a dancer
أنا مجرد راقصة
trying to survive.
محاولة البقاء على قيد الحياة.
You are just a lowly dancer,
أنت مجرد راقص وضيع،
how could you possibly know the princess is afraid of grubs?
كيف يمكنك أن تعرف أن الأميرة تخاف من اليرقات؟
I merely saw you disliked the princess
لقد رأيت فقط أنك لا تحب الأميرة
and meant to ease your worries.
وكان الهدف منه تخفيف مخاوفك.
You do have some wit about you.
لديك بعض الذكاء.
Even if I spare your life today,
حتى لو أبقيت على حياتك اليوم،
what about tomorrow?
وماذا عن الغد؟
Even if I must die tomorrow,
حتى لو كان عليّ أن أموت غداً،
I beg to live today.
أرجو أن أعيش اليوم.
(Qingxian Residence)
(سكن كينغشيان)
Then kneel until tomorrow.
ثم اركع حتى الغد.
Whether you live or die, it shall depend on your fate.
سواء عشت أو مت، فالأمر يعتمد على قدرك.
(Qingxian Residence)
(سكن كينغشيان)
Tonight will feel endlessly long.
ستشعر الليلة بأنها طويلة بلا نهاية.
Xi Yan.
شي يان.
No matter why I've come to look like you,
بغض النظر عن سبب تحولي إلى شكل يشبهك،
I swear
أقسم
(I'll live on for the both of us.)
(سأعيش من أجلنا نحن الاثنين.)
I cannot die yet.
لا يمكنني أن أموت الآن.
I still need to avenge myself
ما زلتُ بحاجة إلى الانتقام لنفسي
and the Shen family.
وعائلة شين.
If Heaven shows no justice,
إذا لم يُظهر السماء العدل،
then I shall be the restless spirit demanding it.
حينها سأكون الروح المضطربة التي تطالب بذلك.
If the world before me is unjust,
إذا كان العالم الذي أمامي ظالماً،
I shall become the vengeful ghost from the abyss.
سأصبح الشبح المنتقم من الهاوية.
If fairness itself is unjust,
إذا كان الإنصاف نفسه ظالماً،
I'll ask the world.
سأسأل العالم.
Letting the good suffer
ترك الأخيار يعانون
while the wicked roam free,
بينما يتجول الأشرار أحراراً،
what kind of justice is that?
أي نوع من العدالة هذا؟
If that lowly maid lives,
إذا كانت تلك الخادمة المتواضعة على قيد الحياة،
my hatred will never fade.
لن يزول كرهي أبداً.
Your Highness, please calm down.
يا صاحب السمو، من فضلك اهدأ.
Anger harms the body.
الغضب يضر بالجسم.
(Nannny, Madam Li) That lowly maid indeed deserves death.
(المربية، السيدة لي) تلك الخادمة الحقيرة تستحق الموت بالفعل.
But how could she possibly know
لكن كيف لها أن تعرف؟
that you fear grubs, Your Highness?
هل تخافون من اليرقات يا صاحب السمو؟
When your father fell in battle, his body was covered in them.
عندما سقط والدك في المعركة، كان جسده مغطى بها.
Very few are aware of this.
قلة قليلة تدرك ذلك.
I'll slap myself.
سأصفع نفسي.
Yu.
يو.
You must punish that maid severely
يجب عليك معاقبة تلك الخادمة بشدة
to win justice for me.
لتحقيق العدالة لي.
If there's nothing more,
إذا لم يكن هناك شيء آخر،
return to the palace early.
العودة إلى القصر مبكراً.
I'm not going back.
لن أعود.
We haven't admired the night pearl
لم نُعجب بلؤلؤة الليل
gifted by the Empress Dowager together yet.
هدية من الإمبراطورة الأرملة، لم يتم تقديمها معًا بعد.
Besides,
بجانب،
I was frightened tonight.
كنت خائفاً الليلة.
I want to stay in the residence.
أريد البقاء في السكن.
Escort Her Highness back to the palace.
رافق صاحبة السمو إلى القصر.
Yes, sir.
نعم سيدي.
Yu.
يو.
Do not make decisions for me again.
لا تتخذ القرارات نيابة عني مرة أخرى.
Not when you haven't even entered my household,
ليس وأنت لم تدخل بيتي حتى،
even after you do,
حتى بعد أن تفعل ذلك،
in this Governor's Residence,
في مقر إقامة الحاكم هذا،
only I
أنا فقط
can decide who lives and who dies.
بإمكانهم أن يقرروا من يعيش ومن يموت.
Yu...
يو...
Your Highness.
صاحب السمو.
So many women in the backyard trying to seduce the Governor.
الكثير من النساء في الفناء الخلفي يحاولن إغواء الحاكم.
Why must you insist on killing Xi Yan alone?
لماذا تصر على قتل شي يان بمفردك؟
The eyes.
العيون.
Your Highness,
صاحب السمو،
what do you mean?
ماذا تقصد؟
That lowly maid's eyes and someone else's
عيون تلك الخادمة المتواضعة وعيون شخص آخر
look exactly the same.
تبدو متطابقة تماماً.
You mean...
تقصد...
Shen Changning.
شين تشانغنينغ.
As long as you live,
ما دمت على قيد الحياة،
my heart will never be at peace.
لن يهدأ قلبي أبداً.
If you wish to kill me,
إذا كنت ترغب في قتلي،
let's see if you have the ability.
دعنا نرى إن كنت تملك القدرة.
Li Wan'er.
لي وان إير.
Sooner or later, I'll trample you beneath my feet.
عاجلاً أم آجلاً، سأدوسك تحت قدمي.
Xi Yan.
شي يان.
All you can do is run your mouth.
كل ما يمكنك فعله هو أن تثرثر.
I am the current imperial princess,
أنا الأميرة الإمبراطورية الحالية،
born of a noble house,
مولود في بيت نبيل،
and granted my title by the Emperor himself.
وقد منحني الإمبراطور نفسه هذا اللقب .
People like you exist only to kneel and serve me.
أمثالكم موجودون فقط ليركعوا ويخدموني.
Before me,
قبلي،
I am the law.
أنا القانون.
I am the rule.
أنا القاعدة.
Just like now,
تمامًا كما هو الحال الآن،
if I dislike your eyes,
إذا لم تعجبني عيناك،
then you can only become blind.
عندها لن يكون أمامك إلا أن تصبح أعمى.
Li Wan'er.
لي وان إير.
You
أنت
are nothing more than a pampered slave
ليسوا أكثر من مجرد عبيد مدللين
kept by those above you.
يحتفظ بها من هم أعلى منك رتبة.
Aren't you afraid that doing too much evil
ألا تخشى أن يؤدي فعل الكثير من الشر إلى
will bring vengeful spirits to claim your life?
هل سيجلب الأرواح الانتقامية لتنتزع حياتك؟
Your Highness.
صاحب السمو.
Are you alright?
هل أنت بخير؟
You wretch!
يا لك من بائس!
Kill her!
اقتلها!
Go!
يذهب!
(Maid, Chunyun) Go now!
(الخادمة، تشون يون) اذهبي الآن!
- Your Highness. - Go now!
- صاحب السمو. - اذهب الآن!
Your Lordship.
صاحب السعادة.
Yu.
يو.
If you cannot discipline your own servants,
إذا لم تستطع تأديب عبيدك،
then I shall discipline them for you.
ثم سأؤدبهم نيابة عنك.
From now on, without my permission,
من الآن فصاعدًا، بدون إذني،
you are forbidden to enter the Governor's Residence.
ممنوع دخولك إلى مقر إقامة الحاكم.
I...
أنا...
Yu.
يو.
♪In youthful days of righteousness♪
في أيام الشباب من الصلاح؟
♪We laughed and made our promise♪
ضحكنا وقطعنا وعدنا.
What a crafty little wench.
يا لها من فتاة ماكرة!
She was kicked out for climbing into his bed before,
طُردت من المنزل لتسللها إلى سريره من قبل.
and now she's won the Governor's favor again.
والآن حازت على رضا الحاكم مرة أخرى.
He's even quarreling with the Princess because of her.
بل إنه يتشاجر مع الأميرة بسببها.
Is the backyard about to descend into chaos?
هل ستتحول الحديقة الخلفية إلى فوضى عارمة؟
♪Looking back upon heaven and earth♪
نظرة إلى الوراء على السماء والأرض
♪How should one remember♪
كيف ينبغي للمرء أن يتذكر؟
♪How should one bid farewell♪
كيف ينبغي للمرء أن يودع؟
Since you're awake,
بما أنك مستيقظ،
stop pretending.
توقف عن التظاهر.
Please don't be offended, Your Lordship.
أرجو ألا تنزعج يا صاحب السعادة.
I simply did not wish to disturb
لم أرغب ببساطة في الإزعاج
your enjoyment of a lady's chamber.
استمتاعك بغرفة سيدة.
To protect yourself,
لحماية نفسك،
you pretended to be weak,
تظاهرت بالضعف،
even harmed yourself.
بل وألحقت الضرر بنفسك.
Your resolve is impressive.
إن عزيمتك مثيرة للإعجاب.
I am low-born.
أنا من أصل متواضع.
To survive,
للبقاء على قيد الحياة،
I can only resort to small tricks.
لا يسعني إلا اللجوء إلى حيل صغيرة.
I beg the your forgiveness, Your Lordship.
أرجو منكم العفو يا صاحب السمو.
I am worth more alive
أنا أستحق أكثر وأنا على قيد الحياة
than dead.
أفضل من الموت.
You understand your situation clearly.
أنت تفهم وضعك بوضوح.
I am merely an insignificant pawn.
أنا مجرد بيدق تافه.
But if used well,
لكن إذا استُخدمت بشكل جيد،
perhaps
ربما
I may become an unexpected asset.
قد أصبح إضافة غير متوقعة.
You carried me back and deliberately let the backyard ladies
لقد حملتني إلى الخلف وتركت سيدات الفناء الخلفي عمداً
see everything.
شاهد كل شيء.
Is it not because
أليس ذلك بسبب
you wish to stir internal conflict?
هل ترغب في إثارة صراع داخلي؟
You seek change.
أنت تسعى للتغيير.
I seek survival.
أسعى للبقاء.
If you protect me,
إذا حميتني،
then I will not fail you.
إذن لن أخذلكم.
Then stir up some storms.
ثم أثير بعض العواصف.
Better than doing nothing.
أفضل من عدم القيام بأي شيء.
(Xi Yan.)
(شي يان.)
(Only after reading your diary,)
(فقط بعد قراءة مذكراتك،)
(I learn that we share the same enemy.)
(أكتشف أننا نتشارك نفس العدو.)
Xi Yan.
شي يان.
The strong possess everything.
الأقوياء يملكون كل شيء.
The weak are mere firewood.
الضعفاء مجرد حطب.
If you wish
إذا كنت ترغب
to survive in this world of beasts,
للبقاء على قيد الحياة في هذا العالم المليء بالوحوش،
you must become like them.
يجب أن تصبح مثلهم.
Even if danger lurks at every step,
حتى لو كان الخطر يتربص في كل خطوة،
I will definitely
سأفعل بالتأكيد
avenge you.
سأنتقم لك.
From this moment on,
من هذه اللحظة فصاعدًا،
I am you.
أنا أنت.
Pei Yu.
باي يو.
Attack an official of the court
الاعتداء على أحد مسؤولي المحكمة
is a crime beyond measure.
إنها جريمة لا يمكن قياسها.
You traitor!
يا خائن!
I'll fight you to the death!
سأقاتلك حتى الموت!
You twist right and wrong
أنت تحرف الصواب والخطأ
and caused over a hundred members of the Shen family
وتسبب ذلك في وفاة أكثر من مائة فرد من عائلة شين
to die unjustly in prison.
أن يموت ظلماً في السجن.
Xiao Huaijin.
شياو هواجين.
Born into the Shen family
ولد في عائلة شين
means only one fate, death.
لا يعني ذلك سوى مصير واحد، وهو الموت.
(I was fooled by appearances.)
(انخدعت بالمظاهر.)
(Words once sweet)
(كلمات كانت حلوة في يوم من الأيام)
(have become poison.)
(أصبحت سامة.)
Li Wan'er.
لي وان إير.
I wish I could tear your sister limb from limb.
أتمنى لو أستطيع تمزيق أختك إرباً إرباً.
Make her maid a prostitute,
اجعل خادمتها عاهرة،
and condemn him to slavery for life.
وحكم عليه بالعبودية مدى الحياة.
(I treated you like my own sister,)
(لقد عاملتك كأختي)
(but never saw your venomous heart.)
(لكنني لم أرَ قلبك السام قط.)
The hypocrite is always arrogant.
المنافق دائماً متغطرس.
The vicious always obsessive.
الشرّاء دائماً مهووس.
The indifferent hide their feelings deepest.
أكثر الناس لامبالاة يخفون مشاعرهم في أعماقهم.
Now I am lowly
أنا الآن متواضع
like an ant,
مثل النملة،
anyone could crush me beneath their feet.
بإمكان أي شخص أن يسحقني تحت قدميه.
You destroyed my family,
لقد دمرت عائلتي،
yet the chance to clear the Shen family's name also lies with you.
لكن فرصة تبرئة اسم عائلة شين تكمن أيضاً في يديك.
Your rank is high.
رتبتك عالية.
Your power immense.
قوتك هائلة.
If I can lure you into my game,
إذا استطعت أن أغريك بالدخول في لعبتي،
and use you as my shield,
وأتخذك درعاً لي،
then whether Xiao Huaijin
ثم ما إذا كان شياو Huaijin
or Li Wan'er,
أو لي وان إير،
I can confront them all.
أستطيع مواجهتهم جميعاً.
I will forge my hatred into a blade
سأحول كراهيتي إلى نصل
and strike down every enemy.
واقضِ على كل عدو.
(Episode Ends)
(انتهت الحلقة)
When did I ever say
متى قلت ذلك؟
that Shen Changning died of poison?
هل مات شين تشانغنينغ مسموماً؟
(Her every word and action)
(كل كلمة وفعل لها)
(is completely different from the person)
(يختلف تماماً عن الشخص)
(I once saw at Xichun House.)
(رأيت ذلك مرة في منزل شيتشون.)
♪Loneliness♪
الشعور بالوحدة
♪How do I cross it?♪
كيف أعبرها؟
♪Whom have I ever failed♪
من خذلتُ في حياتي؟
♪Incense burns through a few sticks♪
يحرق البخور بضع أعواد فقط؟
♪Can the rest of my life be redeemed?♪
هل يمكن إصلاح ما تبقى من حياتي؟
♪The flowing years pass through desolation♪
تمر السنين المتدفقة عبر الخراب.
♪Unwilling to forgive past mistakes♪
غير راغب في مسامحة أخطاء الماضي؟
♪Blaming myself for not protecting♪
ألوم نفسي لعدم حمايتي لنفسي.
♪Our vows as I should have♪
عهودنا كما ينبغي لي أن أفعل.
♪Sorrow♪
؟؟؟حزن؟؟؟
♪Counting it carefully♪
???أحصيها بعناية؟
♪Who stayed by my side through hardship♪
من بقي بجانبي في الشدائد؟
♪There will eventually be a pure land♪
سيأتي يومٌ تكون فيه أرضٌ طاهرة.
♪Where all karmic burden is cast away♪
حيث يتم التخلص من كل عبء كارمي
♪Not until worldly splendor fades♪
لن يحدث ذلك إلا بعد أن يزول بريق الدنيا.
♪Can one understand what cuts to the bone♪
هل يمكن للمرء أن يفهم ما الذي يقطع العظم؟
♪At dusk, with white hair♪
عند الغسق، بشعر أبيض؟
♪I still cannot fathom destiny♪
ما زلتُ عاجزاً عن فهم القدر.
♪After countless struggles across the waters♪
بعد صراعات لا حصر لها عبر المياه
♪At last the lotus heart awakens♪
أخيرًا يستيقظ قلب اللوتس!
♪Drifting across three lifetimes♪
???الانجراف عبر ثلاث حيوات؟
♪Just to wait for your once-in-a-thousand-years glance♪
مجرد انتظار لنظرتك التي لا تتكرر إلا مرة كل ألف عام؟
♪The distant mountains fade along the path home♪
تتلاشى الجبال البعيدة على طول الطريق المؤدي إلى المنزل.
♪I walk with you through morning bells and evening drums♪
أسير معك عبر أجراس الصباح وطبول المساء.
♪Our story lies in the mountains♪
قصتنا تكمن في الجبال
♪Like an ink-washed immortal painting♪
???مثل لوحة خالدة مغسولة بالحبر؟؟؟
♪Where blossoms fall♪
أين تتساقط الأزهار؟
♪I'm glad the fragrance in our hearts stays the same♪
أنا سعيد لأن العطر في قلوبنا يبقى كما هو.
♪Youth slips away♪
يتلاشى الشباب تدريجياً
♪Just to wait for your once-in-a-thousand-years glance♪
مجرد انتظار لنظرتك التي لا تتكرر إلا مرة كل ألف عام؟
♪Dreams wander back to the old road where we met♪
تعود الأحلام إلى الطريق القديم حيث التقينا.
♪Watching you gently play the zither♪
أشاهدك وأنت تعزف على آلة الزيثارة برفق.
♪Time rests upon the strings♪
يستقر الزمن على الأوتار.
♪Waiting for someone to brew a pot of tea♪
أنتظر أن يقوم أحدهم بتحضير إبريق شاي؟